Guide to the Christopher Sykes Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers and Photographs, 1909-1971; Series III; 2.29; (6 boxes)
  - Photographs
    - Sykes family and friends, circa 1930s - 1972, undated (Box 31, Folder 364-371)
      Includes photograph of Sykes with King George VI, Queen Elizabeth (Queen Mother), and Princess Elizabeth (Queen Elizabeth II)
    - Sykes family and unidentified home and pet cat, undated (Box 32, Folder 372-388)
    - Sykes family and unidentified homes (possibly one in Dorset) and at horse show, undated (Box 32, Folder 389-392)
    - Holy Week in Seville, Spain, undated (Box 33, Folder 393)
    - Travels in England, France, and Spain, undated (Box 33, Folder 394-403)
    - Sykes visit to Mottisfont, Seaford, and Badlingham, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 404-407)
    - Travels in Syria, undated (Box 34, Folder 408-409)
    - Travels in Israel, undated (Box 34, Folder 410)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 34, Folder 411-413)
- Oversize, 3.67; (2 boxes)
  - Crossroads to Israel, clippings on Israel (Series II), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 414)
  - Crossroads to Israel, reviews (Series II), 1965 (Box 36, Folder 415)
  - Evelyn Waugh: A Biography, reviews (Series II), 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - Nancy: The Life of Lady Astor, galley proofs, corrected (Series II), circa 1972 (Box Oversize Bsd, folder 417)
  - Orde Wingate, maps of India, Pakistan, Ceylon, Burma, Malaya, Indo-China, Eritrea, Somalia, and Ethiopia (Series II), 1953-1955 (Box Oversize Bsd, folder 418)
  - Orde Wingate, Garrison Map of Anglo-Egyptian Sudan (Series II), 1931 (Box Oversize Bsd, folder 419)
  - Orde Wingate, reviews (Series II), 1959 (Box 36, Folder 420)
  - Wassmuss: The German Lawrence, reviews (Series II), 1936 (Box 36, Folder 421)
  - "The Mystery Parcel", draft, typescript carbon, corrected and published version (Series II), 1955 June 30, undated (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - "A People of Poetry, Not Prose", printed version (Series II), 1959 May 5 (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - "Remembering the Duke", printed version (Series II), 1952 September 12 (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - Radio Scripts, publicity and reviews (Series II), 1948-1952 (Box 36, Folder 423)
  - Book reviews, drafts, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected and printed versions (Series II), 1951-1966, undated (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - Letters to the editor (Series II), 1939-1952 (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - "East Africa Force Campaign: Supplementary Report" (Series III), 1941 (Box 35, Folder 424)
  - Clippings of articles about the Sykes family (Series III), 1935-1957 (Box 36, Folder 425)
  - Material relating to Thomas Wentworth Russell (Series III), 1914, 1954, undated (Box Oversize Bsd, folder 418)
  - Musical scores including manuscript of Norman Kay's "The Sailor's Wife" and printed version of Ronald Jamieson's "In a Golden Coach" (Series III), 1953, undated (Box 35, Folder 427)
  - Advertisement from Basilisk Press for reprint of The Kelmscott Chaucer (Series III), undated (Box 35, Folder 426)
  - Camilla Russell as child and Russell family (Series III), 1909-1912, undated (Box 35, Folder 428)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.42; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  Contains nitrate negatives.
  - Box 31, folders 351-354 (Box CS, Folder 429)
  - Box 31, folders 356-363 (Box CS, Folder 430)
  - Box 31, folders 364-371 (Box CS, Folder 431)
  - Box 32, folders 372-388 (Box CS, Folder 432)
  - Box 32, folders 389-392 (Box CS, Folder 433)
  - Box 33, folders 394-403 (Box CS, Folder 434)
  - Box 33, folders 404-405 (Box CS, Folder 435)
  - Box 33, folders 406-407 (Box CS, Folder 436)
  - Box 34, folder 410 (Box CS, Folder 437)
  - Box 34, folder 411 (Box CS, Folder 438)